A Guide to the William J. “Bill” Elvin Collection, 1914-2004, bulk 1963-2003
Virginia Room, Fairfax County Public Library
- Series 2: McLean Providence Journal Subject Files, 1925-2004
  - McLean Business District Pictures [contains photographs], 1968 (Box 22, Folder 83)
  - McLean Central Business District, 1990-1996 (Box 22, Folder 84)
  - McLean Central Park, 1965-2003 (Box 22, Folder 85)
  - McLean Choral Society, 1983-1991 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - McLean Citizens Association, 1980-1989 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - McLean Citizens Association, 1990-1992 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - McLean Citizens Association, 1993-1994 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - McLean Citizens Association, 1995-1996 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - McLean Citizens Association, 1997-1999 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - McLean Citizens Association, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - McLean Citizens Association, 2001 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - McLean Citizens Association, 2002-2003 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - McLean Community Center, 1996-2003 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - McLean Day [contains photographs], 1988-1989 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - McLean Directory, 1970 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - McLean Exxon Mobil, 2001-2002 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - McLean Fire and Rescue, 1956-2000 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - McLean Government, 1973 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - McLean Green, 1965 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - McLean Hamlet, 1995-1998 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - McLean Hardware, 1982-2001 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - McLean High School, 1990-2000 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - McLean History, 1967-2003 (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - McLean Horse Show, 1961 (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - McLean House and Garden Tours, 1961-1997 (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - McLean Institute, Undated (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - McLean, John, 2002 (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - McLean Lions Club, Undated (Box 23, Folder 25)
  - McLean Little League, 1990-2000 (Box 23, Folder 26)
  - McLean, Ned and Evelyn Walsh, 1997-2002 (Box 23, Folder 27)
  - McLean Office Center, 1970 (Box 23, Folder 28)
  - McLean Orchestra, 1983-2002 (Box 23, Folder 29)
  - McLean Post Office, 1961-2001 (Box 23, Folder 30)
  - McLean Presbyterian Church, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 31)
  - McLean Project for the Arts, 1986-2000 (Box 23, Folder 32)
  - McLean Providence Journal, 1967-1986 (Box 23, Folder 33)
  - McLean Real Estate [contains photographs], 1988-1989 (Box 23, Folder 34)
  - McLean Revitalization Corporation, 2002 (Box 23, Folder 35)
  - McLean River [contains photographs], 1987 (Box 23, Folder 36)
  - McLean “Sound”, 1977-1995 (Box 23, Folder 37)
  - McLean Sports, Undated (Box 23, Folder 38)
  - McLean Square Mall, 1975-2003 (Box 23, Folder 39)
  - McLean Streets, 1964 (Box 23, Folder 40)
  - McLean Symphony, 1997 (Box 23, Folder 41)
  - McLean Theater Alliance, 1998 (Box 23, Folder 42)
  - McLean Trees, 1982-1999 (Box 23, Folder 43)
  - McLean VFW, 2002 (Box 23, Folder 44)
  - McLean Village, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 45)
  - McLean Wine Festival, Undated (Box 23, Folder 46)
  - McLean Youth Groups, 1969-2003 (Box 23, Folder 47)
  - McLean Youth Soccer, 2002-2003 (Box 23, Folder 48)
  - McSlarrow, Kyle, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 49)
  - Mackall Family, 1955-1999 (Box 23, Folder 50)
  - MacLane, Kathryn, 1993 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Macy, John W. Jr., Undated (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Maddux Estate, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Madeira School, 1988-2002 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Madison of McLean, 1980 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Madison, Dolley, 1971-1974 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Madsen, Frank A., Undated (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Male, Buz, 1994 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Malek, Fred, 1978-1988 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Manger, J. Thomas, 1999 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Mann, Jack, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Mann, Judy, 1997 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Manning, Jay, Undated (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Maplewood, 1958-2000 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Marraco, Tina, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Marriott, 1982-2000 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Mars, Forrest, 1983-2002 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Mars, Virginia, Undated (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Marshall High School, Undated (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Marymount University, 1997 (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - Mason, George, Undated (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - Masonic Temple (Sharon), 1983 (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - Massey, Carlton, 1971-1981 (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - Massey, G. Hubard, Undated (Box 24, Folder 24)
  - Matildaville, 1965 (Box 24, Folder 25)
  - Meadowlark Gardens, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 26)
  - Media General, 1996 (Box 24, Folder 27)
  - Medical History - Fairfax County, 1980 (Box 24, Folder 28)
  - Meese, Ed, 1996 (Box 24, Folder 29)
  - Mendelsohn, Stuart, 1993-2003 (Box 24, Folder 30)
  - Metric Measurements, 1976-1999 (Box 24, Folder 31)
  - Metro, 1971-2002 (Box 24, Folder 32)
  - Metropolitan Washington Airport Authority, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 33)
  - Metropolitan Washington Council of Governments, Undated (Box 24, Folder 34)
  - Metzinger, Arthur, 1998-2000 (Box 24, Folder 35)
  - Michael’s Restaurant, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 36)
  - Michigan, University of (Club), 1991-1994 (Box 24, Folder 37)
  - Military - III Corps, 2003 (Box 24, Folder 38)
  - Miller, Andrew, Undated (Box 24, Folder 39)
  - Miller, Demaris, 1997-2000 (Box 24, Folder 40)
  - Miller, Emilie, 1998 (Box 24, Folder 41)
  - Miller, Harris, Undated (Box 24, Folder 42)
  - Miller, Helen Harris, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 43)
  - Miller, James C., Undated (Box 24, Folder 44)
  - Mills, 1966-1981 (Box 24, Folder 45)
  - Minnich, Lt. Pamela, 1999 (Box 24, Folder 46)
  - Mitchell, Ed, 2003 (Box 24, Folder 47)
  - MITRE Corporation, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 48)
  - Monopole, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 49)
  - Monroe, Jewel, 1997 (Box 24, Folder 50)
  - Montgomery County, 1996 (Box 24, Folder 51)
  - Moon, Rev. Sun Myung, 1997 (Box 24, Folder 52)
  - Moore, Ann, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 53)
  - Moore, Audrey, 1990-2002 (Box 24, Folder 54)
  - Moran, James, 1992-2002 (Box 24, Folder 55)
  - Mormon Church, 1962 (Box 24, Folder 56)
  - Morris, James M., 1997 (Box 24, Folder 57)
  - Morris, Martin, 1999 (Box 24, Folder 58)
  - Morrison, Lt. Timothy, Undated (Box 24, Folder 59)
  - Mort’s Bootery, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 60)
  - Morton, Buck, 1981 (Box 24, Folder 61)
  - Morven Park, 1967 (Box 24, Folder 62)
  - Mosby Highway, 1980 (Box 24, Folder 63)
  - Mothers Against Drunk Driving, 1989 (Box 24, Folder 64)
  - Mount Royal Park, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 65)
  - Mount Vernon, 1977-2000 (Box 24, Folder 66)
  - Moutoux Orchard, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 67)
  - Mudd, Roger, 1996-1999 (Box 24, Folder 68)
  - Mulvancey, Dr. Richard, 1993-1997 (Box 24, Folder 69)
  - Munsey, Everard, Undated (Box 24, Folder 70)
  - Murphy, Sean, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 71)
  - Mutersbaugh, 1965-1995 (Box 24, Folder 72)
  - Myers, Rev. William F., Undated (Box 24, Folder 73)
  - Nassikas, John, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 74)
  - National Association of Retired Federal Employees - McLean Chapter, 1997 (Box 24, Folder 75)
  - National Wildlife Federation, 1997-1998 (Box 24, Folder 76)
  - Nations Bank, 1998 (Box 24, Folder 77)
  - Neal, Jeffry, 1999 (Box 24, Folder 78)
  - Neel, Sam, 1985-2004 (Box 24, Folder 79)
  - Neighbors for a Better Community, 1972 (Box 24, Folder 80)
  - New Dominion Chorale, 1993 (Box 24, Folder 81)
  - Newspapers, 1981 (Box 24, Folder 82)
  - Nike Missiles, 1996 (Box 24, Folder 83)
  - Nipper the Dog, 1995 (Box 24, Folder 84)
  - Noor, Queen of Jordan, 2002 (Box 24, Folder 85)
  - North, Oliver, 1990-1994 (Box 24, Folder 86)
  - Northern Virginia Association for History, Inc, 1997 (Box 24, Folder 87)
  - Northern Virginia Regional Park Authority, 1966-1993 (Box 24, Folder 88)
  - Northern Virginia Training Center, 1977 (Box 24, Folder 89)
  - Northwest Langley Neighborhood Watch, 1984 (Box 24, Folder 90)
  - Noyes, Newbold, 1997 (Box 24, Folder 91)
  - NVR, 1993-1996 (Box 24, Folder 92)
  - Oakcrest School, 1999-2000 (Box 24, Folder 93)
  - Oatlands, 1989 (Box 24, Folder 94)
  - Obermayer, Herman, 1997 (Box 24, Folder 95)
  - Obituaries A-C, 1983-1987 (Box 24, Folder 96)
  - Obituaries D-F, 1982-1987 (Box 24, Folder 97)
  - Obituaries G-I, 1982-1987 (Box 24, Folder 98)
  - Obituaries J-L, 1982-1987 (Box 24, Folder 99)
  - Obituaries M-O, 1982-1987 (Box 24, Folder 100)
  - Obituaries P-R, 1982-1986 (Box 24, Folder 101)
  - Obituaries S-V, 1982-1987 (Box 24, Folder 102)
  - Obituaries W-Z, 1982-1987 (Box 24, Folder 103)
  - Occoquan, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 104)
  - Odrick, Alfred, 2001-2002 (Box 24, Folder 105)
  - Old Dominion Citizens Association, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 106)
  - Old Dominion Drive, 1977-2001 (Box 24, Folder 107)
  - Olin, Charles, 2002 (Box 24, Folder 108)
  - Olney Park (Pimmit Run), 1978 (Box 24, Folder 109)
  - O’Neill, Robert J. Jr, 1997 (Box 24, Folder 110)
  - Open Space, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 111)
  - Optimist Club, 1958 (Box 24, Folder 112)
  - O’Toole’s [contains photographs], 1989 (Box 24, Folder 113)
  - Outer Beltway, 1965-1966 (Box 24, Folder 114)
  - Owen, Ferris, 1984 (Box 24, Folder 115)
  - Ox Hill, 1995 (Box 24, Folder 116)
  - Painter, Barbara, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 117)
  - Palladium, 2003 (Box 24, Folder 118)
  - Pari-Mutuel Horse Racing, 1978-1979 (Box 24, Folder 119)
  - Parkouts (Trash), 2001-2002 (Box 24, Folder 120)
  - Parks, 1991 (Box 24, Folder 121)
  - Patowmack Canal, 1990 (Box 24, Folder 122)
  - Patten, Cheryl Ball, Undated (Box 24, Folder 123)
  - Payne, L.F., 1999 (Box 24, Folder 124)
  - Payne, Parke “Ned”, 1991 (Box 24, Folder 125)
  - Peacock House, Undated (Box 24, Folder 126)
  - Peed, Carl, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 127)
  - Pennino, Walter, 1991 (Box 24, Folder 128)
  - Pentagon, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 129)
  - Perlick, William, 1964 (Box 24, Folder 130)
  - Perper, Martin, 1977 (Box 24, Folder 131)
  - Pett, Saul, 1993 (Box 24, Folder 132)
  - Pettinger, Robert, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 133)
  - Phillips, Barbara, 1999-2000 (Box 24, Folder 134)
  - Phillips, Rufus, 1971-2000 (Box 24, Folder 135)
  - Phoenix, Ruth, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 136)
  - Pickens, Caroline, 2002 (Box 24, Folder 137)
  - Pimmit Freeway, 1966-1969 (Box 24, Folder 138)
  - Pimmit Hills, 1977-2000 (Box 24, Folder 139)
  - Pimmit Run, 1965-1971 (Box 24, Folder 140)
  - Plane Crash, 1977 (Box 24, Folder 141)
  - Planning Research Corporation, 1980-1992 (Box 24, Folder 142)
  - Pleasant Grove, 1999-2003 (Box 24, Folder 143)
  - Plum, Ken, 1977-1979 (Box 24, Folder 144)
  - Poling, Harold, 1994 (Box 24, Folder 145)
  - Polio Vaccine, 1993 (Box 24, Folder 146)
  - Poole, Richard, 1993 (Box 24, Folder 147)
  - Population Growth, 1976-2002 (Box 24, Folder 148)
  - Postmaster of McLean, 2002-2003 (Box 24, Folder 149)
  - Potomac River, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 150)
  - Potomac School, 1987-2003 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Potomac Vegetable, 1998 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Powell, Colin, 1996 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Power, 2001 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Price, Ann, 1999 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Prichard, Edgar, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Prince Bandar Bin Sultan, 1992 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Prisons, 1992 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - PRM - Planned Residential Mixed Use Development, 2001 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Providence Baptist Church, 1985-2000 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Public Roads, 1982-1983 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Pulte Homes, 2001 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Quayle, Dan, 1988 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Radon, 1990-1992 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Railroads, 1966-2000 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Raleigh, Elizabeth, 1986-1999 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Randall, Cortes, 1980 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Randall, H. Gordon, Undated (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Recreation, 1962-1993 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Recycling, 1993 (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Redistricting, 1965-1966 (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - Reiber, Paul and Kristin Harris, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - Reid, C.E. Larry, 1996 (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - Reid, James Wallace, 1996 (Box 25, Folder 24)
  - Religious School, 1989 (Box 25, Folder 25)
  - Republicans, 1975-1996 (Box 25, Folder 26)
  - Reserve, The, 1998 (Box 25, Folder 27)
  - Reston, 1965-2001 (Box 25, Folder 28)
  - Revelle, Red, 1998 (Box 25, Folder 29)
  - Rhodes, James T., Undated (Box 25, Folder 30)
  - Richards, Donald G., 1998 (Box 25, Folder 31)
  - Richards, Lilla, 1977-1998 (Box 25, Folder 32)
  - Richardson, Anne, 1999 (Box 25, Folder 33)
  - Richardson, Elliott, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 34)
  - Rickover Foundation, 1983-1984 (Box 25, Folder 35)
  - Ridder, Marie, 1982-2000 (Box 25, Folder 36)
  - Rieger, Donie, 1977-1996 (Box 25, Folder 37)
  - Riggs Bank, Undated (Box 25, Folder 38)
  - Rising Stars Concerts, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 39)
  - Ritz-Carlton, 1991 (Box 25, Folder 40)
  - River Farm, Undated (Box 25, Folder 41)
  - River View, Undated (Box 25, Folder 42)
  - Riverbend Park, 2001-2002 (Box 25, Folder 43)
  - Road Names, 1964-1987 (Box 25, Folder 44)
  - Robb, Charles, 1981-1994 (Box 25, Folder 45)
  - Robeson, Palmer, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 46)
  - Rockefeller, Sharon, 1997 (Box 25, Folder 47)
  - Rockwell, George Lincoln, Undated (Box 25, Folder 48)
  - Rodef Shalom, 1970-1994 (Box 25, Folder 49)
  - Roehner, Frederic, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 50)
  - Rokeby Farm, 1998 (Box 25, Folder 51)
  - Roosevelt, James, 1991 (Box 25, Folder 52)
  - Rosenbaum, Albert, 1994 (Box 25, Folder 53)
  - Rosenbaum, Robert, 2001 (Box 25, Folder 54)
  - Rotary Club of McLean, 1966-2003 (Box 25, Folder 55)
  - Rotunda Condominiums, 1976-1980 (Box 25, Folder 56)
  - Roundabout, 2001-2002 (Box 25, Folder 57)
  - Rowe, Ruth, Undated (Box 25, Folder 58)
  - Rumpf, Robert, 1994 (Box 25, Folder 59)
  - Runyon, Charles, 1969 (Box 25, Folder 60)
  - Rust, John H. Jr, 1982-1998 (Box 25, Folder 61)
  - Ryan, Mrs. Lawrence, 1967 (Box 25, Folder 62)
  - Safe Community Coalition, 2001-2002 (Box 25, Folder 63)
  - Safeway - Andre Wye, 1995 (Box 25, Folder 64)
  - St. John’s Catholic Church, 1993 (Box 25, Folder 65)
  - St. John’s Episcopal Church, 1956-1996 (Box 25, Folder 66)
  - Sales Tax, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 67)
  - Salk, Jonas, 1982-1995 (Box 25, Folder 68)
  - Salona, 1979-2000 (Box 25, Folder 69)
  - Salvation Army, 1981-1983 (Box 25, Folder 70)
  - Sam’s Sunoco, 1997 (Box 25, Folder 71)
  - Sanders, David, Undated (Box 25, Folder 72)
  - Sanders, Milburn, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 73)
  - Santa Balla, Jose, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 74)
  - Saudi Arabia, 1992-1993 (Box 25, Folder 75)
  - Sawmelle, Miriam, 1994 (Box 25, Folder 76)
  - Scattergood, Margaret, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 77)
  - Schanke, Gerald, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 78)
  - Schar, Dwight, 1990-2002 (Box 25, Folder 79)
  - Schmitz Exxon, 1980 (Box 25, Folder 80)
  - Schoene, Les, 1997 (Box 25, Folder 81)
  - School Integration, 1964 (Box 25, Folder 82)
  - Schools, Charles, 1984 (Box 25, Folder 83)
  - Schools - Back to School, 1989 (Box 25, Folder 84)
  - Schools - Budget, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 85)
  - Schools - Feature Articles [contains photographs], 1989-1991 (Box 25, Folder 86)
  - Schools - Little Langley, 1989 (Box 25, Folder 87)
  - Schools - McLean High School [contains photographs], 1987-1990 (Box 25, Folder 88)
  - Schools - Merit Based Pay, 1986-1989 (Box 25, Folder 89)
  - Schools - Middle Schools, 1988-1989 (Box 25, Folder 90)
  - Schools - Miscellaneous, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 91)
  - Schools - Schedule Restructuring, 1988-1989 (Box 25, Folder 92)
  - Schools - Security, 1989 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Schools - Sexual Education, 1986-1989 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Schools - Student Membership, 1987-1988 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Schools - The New School of Northern Virginia, 1989 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Schrott, John D., Jr., 1982 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Scott, James "Jim", 1991-1998 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Scott, William, 1997 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Scotts Run, 1992 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Sears Homes, 1981-2001 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Security, 1981-1990 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Seeley, Martha, 1988-1999 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - September Club, Undated (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Settler’s Clan, 1990 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Severance, Charles, 1996-1999 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Sewers, 1971-1975 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Shacochis, John, Helen, and Bob, 1975-2004 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Shafer, Hugh, 1967 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Shafran, George, Undated (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Share, Inc, 1997 (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Sharon Estate, Undated (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Sharon Masonic Temple, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Shaw, Harold "Ranger Hal", 1999 (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - Shelp, Page, 1999 (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - Sheraton Hotel, 1989 (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - Sherk, Grant, Undated (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - Sherman, Nellie, 1998 (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - Sherwood, John, Undated (Box 26, Folder 27)
  - Shiloh Baptist Church, Undated (Box 26, Folder 28)
  - Short, Lawrence, Undated (Box 26, Folder 29)
  - Shouse, Catherine F., 1966-2000 (Box 26, Folder 30)
  - Smith Park, 1997 (Box 26, Folder 31)
  - Smith, Judge Howard, Undated (Box 26, Folder 32)
  - Smith, Richard M., 1968 (Box 26, Folder 33)
  - Smithsonian, 1996 (Box 26, Folder 34)
  - Smyth, Linda, 1999-2003 (Box 26, Folder 35)
  - Solid Waste, 1989 (Box 26, Folder 36)
  - Sorensen, Ted, Undated (Box 26, Folder 37)
  - Spannaus, Nancy, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 38)
  - Spong, William, 1997 (Box 26, Folder 39)
  - Spring Hill, 1985-2002 (Box 26, Folder 40)
  - Spring Hill Soccer, 2003 (Box 26, Folder 41)
  - Stadium (Redskins), 1992 (Box 26, Folder 42)
  - Stamps and Coins, 1982 (Box 26, Folder 43)
  - Starr, Kenneth, 1996-2004 (Box 26, Folder 44)
  - Staybridge Hotel, 1999-2000 (Box 26, Folder 45)
  - Stell, Bill, 1995 (Box 26, Folder 46)
  - Stitt, David T., Undated (Box 26, Folder 47)
  - Storm Farm, Undated (Box 26, Folder 48)
  - Storm Store, 2001 (Box 26, Folder 49)
  - Streetcars, Undated (Box 26, Folder 50)
  - Stuntz, Mayo, 1997-2003 (Box 26, Folder 51)
  - Sully Plantation, 1965-2000 (Box 26, Folder 52)
  - Summers, George, 1994 (Box 26, Folder 53)
  - Sunrise Assisted Living, 2002-2003 (Box 26, Folder 54)
  - Sunset Hill, 1963 (Box 26, Folder 55)
  - Sutcliffe, Joyce, 1986-1987 (Box 26, Folder 56)
  - Sutherland, David A., 1969 (Box 26, Folder 57)
  - Swinson, James, 1967-1997 (Box 26, Folder 58)
  - Tabler, Charles B., 1967 (Box 26, Folder 59)
  - Taima, Fuad K., 1999-2000 (Box 26, Folder 60)
  - Taxes, 1978-2003 (Box 26, Folder 61)
  - Taylor, Elizabeth, 1977 (Box 26, Folder 62)
  - Teen Center, 1990 (Box 26, Folder 63)
  - Telephone Service, Undated (Box 26, Folder 64)
  - Temple Rodef Shalom, 1970-2003 (Box 26, Folder 65)
  - Ternisky, Dr. Mike, 1990 (Box 26, Folder 66)
  - Terpil, Frank, 1983-1995 (Box 26, Folder 67)
  - Thillman, John, 1997 (Box 26, Folder 68)
  - Thoburn, John, 1979-2002 (Box 26, Folder 69)
  - Thoburn, Lloyd, 1987 (Box 26, Folder 70)
  - Thoesen, Richard C., 2000-2003 (Box 26, Folder 71)
  - Thomas, Hugh Reilly, 1997 (Box 26, Folder 72)
  - Thompson, Charles C., 1999 (Box 26, Folder 73)
  - Thompson, Pauline, 1996 (Box 26, Folder 74)
  - Threadgill, Gene, 1965-1996 (Box 26, Folder 75)
  - Tighe, Kevin, 2000 (Box 26, Folder 76)
  - Times Community Newspapers, Undated (Box 26, Folder 77)
  - Tobacco, 1998 (Box 26, Folder 78)
  - Toone, Kenneth, 1999 (Box 26, Folder 79)
  - Towlston, 1996-2001 (Box 26, Folder 80)
  - Traffic, 1980 (Box 26, Folder 81)
  - Trails, 1963-1978 (Box 26, Folder 82)
  - Trammel, French Alexander, 1996 (Box 26, Folder 83)
  - Transportation, 1984-1990 (Box 26, Folder 84)
  - Trapnell, Christine, 1995 (Box 26, Folder 85)
  - Trees, 1978-1999 (Box 26, Folder 86)
  - Trible, Rosemary, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 87)
  - Trinity United Methodist Church, 2001 (Box 26, Folder 88)
  - Truaux, Mary, 2001 (Box 26, Folder 89)
  - TRW, 1983-1997 (Box 26, Folder 90)
  - Tucker, S.W., 2000 (Box 26, Folder 91)
  - Turberville, 1971 (Box 26, Folder 92)
  - Turner Farm/Nike Park, 1997-2000 (Box 26, Folder 93)
  - Turner, Mark, Undated (Box 26, Folder 94)
  - Tysons Firehouse, 2002 (Box 26, Folder 95)
  - Tysons Library, 1983-1985 (Box 26, Folder 96)
  - Tysons National Bank, Undated (Box 26, Folder 97)
  - Tysons Tower Club, 1988-2003 (Box 26, Folder 98)
  - Tysons Town Center, 1998-2003 (Box 26, Folder 99)
  - U.S. Geological Survey, 1971-1977 (Box 26, Folder 100)
  - U.S. Supreme Court, 2000 (Box 26, Folder 101)
  - Udall Family, 1971-2002 (Box 26, Folder 102)
  - Ulfelder (Maplewood), 1958-1997 (Box 26, Folder 103)
  - United Virginia Bank, 1991 (Box 26, Folder 104)
  - United Way, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 105)
  - University of Virginia - Northern Virginia Center, 1957-1997 (Box 26, Folder 106)
  - Utitlities, 1958-2002 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Van Winkle, Margaret (Maggie), Undated (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Veterans, 1981-2002 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Vick, Molly, Undated (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Vickery, Raymond, 1992 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Victims, 1996 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Vienna Trust Company, 1958 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Vinson Hall, 1967-1999 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Virginia, 1966-1990 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Virginia Department of Motor Vehicles, 1990 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Virginia Department of Transportation, 1981-1999 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Virginia General Assembly, 1987-1999 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Virginia Potpourri, Undated (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Virginia Power, 1989-1992 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Voight, Mairanne, 1993 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Volunteer Center of Fairfax County, 1996 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Waddell, Charles, 1979-1983 (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Wahl, John A., 1975-2000 (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Wahlquist, Andrew, 1988-1990 (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - Walde, William L., 1994 (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - Walker, Preston, 1978 (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - Walney Farm, 1981 (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - Walsh, Raymond V., Jr., 1971 (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - Walters, Harry N., 1982 (Box 27, Folder 24)
  - Walters, Patricia, Undated (Box 27, Folder 25)
  - Walton, Ed, 1996 (Box 27, Folder 26)
  - Warner, John, 1996 (Box 27, Folder 27)
  - Warner, Mark, 1996-2001 (Box 27, Folder 28)
  - Warnke, Paul C., 1982 (Box 27, Folder 29)
  - Washburn, Karen, 2000 (Box 27, Folder 30)
  - Washington and Old Dominion Trail, 1976-2000 (Box 27, Folder 31)
  - Washington, George, 1982 (Box 27, Folder 32)
  - Waterford, 1982 (Box 27, Folder 33)
  - Watergate, Undated (Box 27, Folder 34)
  - Watters, William, 1994 (Box 27, Folder 35)
  - Weather - Hurricane Agnes, 1972 (Box 27, Folder 36)
  - Webb, John C., 2000 (Box 27, Folder 37)
  - Weed, Curtis M., 1984 (Box 27, Folder 38)
  - Wehner, Harrison, 1997 (Box 27, Folder 39)
  - Weinberger, Caspar, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 40)
  - Welch, Bernard, Undated (Box 27, Folder 41)
  - West Falls Church Metro Station, 1972-2000 (Box 27, Folder 42)
  - West Group, 1985-2003 (Box 27, Folder 43)
  - West McLean, 1988-1992 (Box 27, Folder 44)
  - Westgate, 1964-1996 (Box 27, Folder 45)
  - Westpark, 1963-1968 (Box 27, Folder 46)
  - Westwood, 1980-1982 (Box 27, Folder 47)
  - White, Dr. Ruth, 1994 (Box 27, Folder 48)
  - White, Jean Van Devanter, 2000 (Box 27, Folder 49)
  - White, Justice Byron, 1983-2002 (Box 27, Folder 50)
  - Who's Who in McLean, 1976 (Box 27, Folder 51)
  - Whyte, Adrienne, 2003 (Box 27, Folder 52)
  - Wilhelm, Jane, 2002 (Box 27, Folder 53)
  - Wilkins, Anne, 1965-1996 (Box 27, Folder 54)
  - Williams, Earle, C., 1992-1993 (Box 27, Folder 55)
  - Williams, Randolph, 1987-2002 (Box 27, Folder 56)
  - Windy Hill Farm, 1971 (Box 27, Folder 57)
  - Winfield, Mike, 1994 (Box 27, Folder 58)
  - Wing, Martha, 1998 (Box 27, Folder 59)
  - Wolf, Frank, 1990-1993 (Box 27, Folder 60)
  - Wolf Trap Farm Park, 1968-1984 (Box 27, Folder 61)
  - Woman's Club of McLean, 1970-1996 (Box 27, Folder 62)
  - Women's Center, 2002 (Box 27, Folder 63)
  - Woodbine, 1984 (Box 27, Folder 64)
  - World War II, 1991-1994 (Box 27, Folder 65)
  - Wrenn, Suzie, 1993 (Box 27, Folder 66)
  - Young, Robert, 1984-1999 (Box 27, Folder 67)
  - Youth, 1965-1981 (Box 27, Folder 68)
  - Zanfagna, Philip E., Jr., 2000 (Box 27, Folder 69)
- Series 3: Photographs, 1956-2003
  - Alexander, Joseph, 1981 (Box 28)
  - Andrews, Bob - with Bill Elvin and Aggie Wolf, 1997 December 7 (Box 28)
  - Angle, Wayne, Undated (Box 28)
  - Bermingham, Philip with Queen Elizabeth II, Undated (Box 28)